How to post
variable prices
Ashley Christian  ·  Groundbreaker Marketing
How do I put
that on my
website?
If it's a
variable or
we have different
prices for
different size
tanks
it's fine to give
a range if you
have the bottom
and the top of
what you'll
charge for a pump
out put that in
there or some
people will do
it's X amount for
the first
thousand gallons
and then X amount
after that
everyone has a
different way
that they price
and there's a lot
of different ways
but there's
usually several
tiers so it's
fine to just list
the tiers it's
fine to say
starting at your
lowest price and
then not list
anything else
The point here is
not to get super
in the weeds
about exactly
which prices
you're
publishing
but you're trying
to basically get
just your prices
out there
even if it's your
starting price or
if it's a range